quiz = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "1: 08/09 - 14/15 ",
        "answer" : "Robinson"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "2: 01/02 - 06/07 ",
        "answer" : "Neill"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "3: 94/95 - 97/98 ",
        "answer" : "Kenna"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "4: 07/08 - 11/12 ",
        "answer" : "Samba"
    },
    5 : {
        "question" : "5: 03/04 ",
        "answer" : "Amoruso"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "6: 12/13 - 16/17 ",
        "answer" : "Lowe"
    },
    7 : {
        "question" : "7: 13/14 - 14/15 ",
        "answer" : "King"
    },
    8 : {
        "question" : "8: 08/09 - 14/15  ",
        "answer" : "Dunn"
    },
    9 : {
        "question" : "9: 05/06 ",
        "answer" : "Kuqi"
    },
    10 : {
        "question" : "10: 17/18 - 19/20 ",
        "answer" : "Graham"
    },
    11 : {
        "question" : "11: 12/13 - 15/16 ",
        "answer" : "Rhodes"
    },
    12 : {
        "question" : "12: 04/05 - 12/13 ",
        "answer" : "Pedersen"
    },
    13 : {
        "question" : "13: 12/13 ",
        "answer" : "Murphy"
    },
    14 : {
        "question" : "14: 15/16 ",
        "answer" : "Gomez"
    },
    15 : {
        "question" : "15: 04/05 - 08/09 ",
        "answer" : "Mokoena"
    },
    16 : {
        "question" : "16: 11/12 - 13/14 ",
        "answer" : "Dann"
    },
    17 : {
        "question" : "17: 12/13 - 15/16 ",
        "answer" : "Williamson"
    },
    18 : {
        "question" : "18: 00/01 - 02/03 ",
        "answer" : "Gillespie"
    },
    19 : {
        "question" : "19: 17/18 ",
        "answer" : "Payne"
    },
    20 : {
        "question" : "20: 02/03 - 04/05 ",
        "answer" : "Thompson"
    },
    21 : {
        "question" : "21: 12/13 ",
        "answer" : "Gomes"
    },
    22 : {
        "question" : "22: 17/18 - 18/19 ",
        "answer" : "Gladwin"
    },
    23 : {
        "question" : "23: 09/10 - 11/12 ",
        "answer" : "Hoilett"
    },
    24 : {
        "question" : "24: 03/04 ",
        "answer" : "Ferguson"
    },
    25 : {
        "question" : "25: 14/15 ",
        "answer" : "Tunnicliffe"
    },
    26 : {
        "question" : "26: 09/10 ",
        "answer" : "Di Santo"
    },
    27 : {
        "question" : "27: 09/10 - 10/11  ",
        "answer" : "Salgado"
    },
    28 : {
        "question" : "28: 09/10 - 10/11 ",
        "answer" : "Jones"
    },
    29 : {
        "question" : "29: 13/14 - 20/21 ",
        "answer" : "Evans"
    },
    30 : {
        "question" : "30: 09/10 ",
        "answer" : "Rigters"
    },
    31 : {
        "question" : "31: 10/11 - 12/13 ",
        "answer" : "Hanley"
    }
}